Hello, everyone.
Welcome to tonight's
office hour.
Tonight is just me and Will,
so no Shin, but
hopefully we'll do well,
just the two of us. Will,
do you want to say hi?
Hello, everyone.
I don't know if Shin
gave us anything
that we were supposed
to mention this time.
I don't know what
week number it is.
Me neither.
But here we'll go.
it didn't look like
there were any questions
yet so I'm sort of looking
up just seeing where
we should be right now
yeah but also the main
topic of this office hour
is for us to provide the
solution of assignment 6
this is true and then of
course if in the meantime
you have any questions and
you want to post them in ad
we will take care of them
after that so let
me start sharing
and thank you to
the person that
that shared that it
is week 13. Thank you.
Thank you.
Somebody's counting.
So I was saying very close
to the end, much more
than the beginning, but
I wouldn't have said the
week. But we didn't do
13 office hours. I think
this includes the two weeks
that we had the spring
break and the ********.
Okay, so let me share my
screen in the meantime,
because if you want to say
something, because I am
clearly not multitasking.
so before i start sharing
a random other document
i let you say something
okay yeah so we're uh
got the answers all set
up for you so and we can
see it now okay perfect so
you see the document and
nothing else that's perfect
okay so um i'm starting
with the with the
solution but as i said In
the meantime, if you have
any comment or question,
Will is monitoring the
post on the office hour, so
feel free to ask through
that. And I will say, keep
in mind, when we say the
answer, these are sample
answers. There are any
number of ways you could
have solved several of
these. So we're giving you a
sample of how it could have
been solved, not necessarily
saying you have to have
exactly this or you
won't get points. Yeah, and
I will repeat it 3 million
times. This is just a
possible solution, right?
Somehow, I think one of
the easiest way to solve
it, because you can
overcomplicate if you look
at the way in which you
said it, or you could have
solved it in a little,
slightly different way.
But I think that looking
through a possible
solution gives you an
idea of the direction
you should have taken
with your solution.
Okay, so let's start
with task number one.
And so the task was
asking you to create
a method that
contain a division by
zero fault and at
least two branches,
such that every possible
test suite that reveal
the fault achieve 100%
statement coverage, and
it's possible to create
a test suite that achieve
100% branch coverage and
does not reveal the fault.
Now, one of the problems
with this one, sorry,
one of the problems with
this one is just to be
aware that there is a
difference between every
possible test suite that
reveals the fault, achieves
100% statement coverage, and
every possible test suite
that achieves 100% statement
coverage reveals the
fault. This is not saying
every 100% statement
coverage has to find the
fault. It says you can't find
the fault with less than
100% statement coverage.
yeah exactly because if it
was the other way around
one could say okay how
is it possible that this
happened and there is a
test suite that achieve 100%
coverage and that's not
refill the fault but this is
not saying that every test
suite that reveal the fault
it doesn't say every test
suite that achieve 100%
coverage reveal the fault
it's say the other way
around it's say every test
suite that reveal default
achieve 100% coverage okay
that's so now a possible
solution right how do you
start the idea is this it
the suggestion is that as
there are at least two branches
so ideally you try to
see if you know you can
just do it with two branches
right and now because it
says every possible test
suite that reveal default
achieve 100% statement
coverage ideally one could say
okay so i have two branches
in one nothing happened
and in the other there is
this statement that can
create a fault okay and
so this is how we built a
possible solution and i um
i will repeat it million
times um we'll say it at
the beginning but it applies
all the way so in our
solution what we decide to
say is that at the end
right we have a division
one divided by a and so we
have two branches in one
we manipulate the value of
a in the other we do nothing
and that means that there
might be way in which we
manipulate the value of a
in this in in the branch
where there is the statement
in which we can make it
become zero and so it means
that when a becomes zero,
since if you look at our graph,
every time we go and
manipulate the value
of a, we cover all
the statement, right?
And our condition requires
that a to go in the false
branch, that a is less than
zero. So when we arrive at
the division by A here, we
arrive either manipulating
the value of A, and in that
case, there is a situation
in which A can become zero,
or we arrive in this direction
and A is always less than
zero, so it's never equal
to zero. So the only way
to have a division by zero
is to go in the branch, is
to cover all the statement.
And it happens just
when A is equal to one.
So every time, so in
order to reveal the fault,
I have to have a test case
that is A equal to one.
But I can cover all the
branches without choosing
A equal to one as a
value, right? because, for
instance, I can choose
A equal to 0 and A equal
to minus 1, or I can
choose A equal to 10 and A
equal to minus 7. I cover
all the branches, but
I don't reveal the fault.
But every time I include
A equal to 1, I'm covering
all the statement.
So every time I reveal
the fault, I have covered
all the statement as was
requested by the task.
Will, do you want
to add anything?
Nope.
If you want to go
up and just show
them what the code
looks like, too.
It was up. Yeah.
Yes. Right there.
You know, I'm a visual
person, so the graph speaks
to me much more than
the code. But yes. And I
tend to be much more
of a code person, so I
figured you probably have
some of each in the class,
so it's good to show them
both. Maybe I can manage
to have both at the
same time in the screen.
Almost.
Almost. Yay.
But you can basically see
the same situation. is
the only way you can reach
it is passing in one,
which does create 100%
statement coverage. So you
can't do it in less than
100% statement coverage.
And yet if you pass in
two and zero, you won't
find it, but you'll have
created branch coverage.
Two and minus one.
Or two and zero.
No. Oh, no, two and minus
one. Sorry, it's greater
than or equal to. yes because
if you would include the
zero here so if a was
greater than zero my dyslexic
brain didn't see the
greater than or equal to it
just so yeah i'm telling
you the graph is your friend
okay let's go to task number
two uh okay task number
two was asking uh to
against the usual things to
create a method call unstable
method two that contains
a division by zero fault
and at least two branches
such that every possible
test suite that achieve
100% branch coverage reveal
the fault and it is not
possible to create a test
suite that achieve less
than 100% statement coverage
and reveal the fault
so let's read it again so
every possible test suite
that achieve 100% branch
coverage, reveal default.
But at the same time,
it is not possible
to create a test suite
that doesn't cover
all the statements
and reveal default.
So if we think about what
we had before, we are
in a similar situation,
right? Because we have two
branches, right? And if
we think in the simplest
way, we can say, okay, so
I cannot develop the else
branch. And so I have a
branch in which I have
a statement and a branch
in which I don't have it
if the
fault was where
nothing happened so
where there are no
statement I could
reach I could find
the default without
reaching the without
getting 100% statement
coverage so again yeah,
I need to be able to
cover all the statement
to find the fault. So
in this way, we did it
as simple as possible.
And we just say, okay,
so let's do the most
simple way is like, okay,
if A is equal to zero,
I divided one by A.
And that means that, you
know, to reveal the fault,
I need to execute this
statement and it's not
possible to find this fault
unless I execute all the
statement. On the other
hand, every time I cover all
the branches, I also cover
this one and so I always
reveal the fault because
it doesn't, whenever I go
in the then branch so
on this side i go with a
single value so i to go on
this side i i need to have
a equal to zero so to cover
all the branches i have
to have a equal one one
test case in which a equal
to zero and one test case
in which a is different
from zero and it doesn't
really matter the value
which a is different from
zero but every time i cover
this this branch i reveal
the fault and i I cannot
reveal the fault unless
I cover this branch. And
when I cover this branch,
I cover all the statement.
Will, I'll show the code.
Yeah.
Basically,
you've got one branch that
you always will reveal
the fault any time you
go into that branch.
And the other branch
doesn't contain
anything. So you can't
execute the fault
and not have hit
all the statements.
And think about this. You
say every possible test
suite that achieves 100
% branch coverage will be
the fault. And so we put
the fault in a position
in a way that every time
you go down that branch,
to go down that branch,
you have always the
same value, right?
Because if it was more
articulated like in
the previous example,
then you could
cover that branch
with different
values of A, right?
And before, we were just
decremented the value of
A. Here it's really,
really simple. Every time A
is equal to zero, you go
in the then branch. And
in that branch, you
divided one by A. That is
equal to zero. And actually,
you could do this even
slightly more simply if
you passed in a boolean.
And if the Boolean
was true, you have int
a equals 1. If the
Boolean is true, it's 0.
a equals 1 over a.
It would be the same
situation, but it'd be even
simpler because there'd be
only two things you could
pass in. You don't get
confused by, oh, well, but
there's a zillion different
a's I could pass in.
Yeah.
Yeah, but yes. But the
fact is just to, yeah.
I may just be confusing
things. I'm sorry.
It's okay. No, it's fine.
Because I think that the
key here is that to cover
all the branches, you need
to pick A equal to zero
and A different from zero.
When you pick A equal to
zero, you reveal the fault.
And so there is no
other way you can cover
all the branches. So
every time you cover
all the branches,
you reveal the fault.
And to reveal the fault,
you need to cover all
the statement because the
fault is on this side.
not on the side where
nothing happened.
Okay, third task.
Again, create a method
called unstable method
three, third task,
that contain a division
by zero fault and at
least two branches so
that every possible
task suite that achieves
100% statement coverage
reveals the fault.
And it is possible to
create a task suite that
achieves 100% path coverage
and does not reveal default
will thoughts this this
is not possible and in
order to receive full points
on this one you had to
adequately describe that
it is not possible and
essentially you had to
describe subsumption because
essentially what it means
is because path coverage
subsumes branch coverage
and branch coverage subsume
statement coverage. Therefore,
every path coverage,
100% path coverage test suite
will also be 100% statement
coverage. So therefore,
any path coverage that did
not reveal the fault would
have to not reveal the
fault because it was path
coverage, but also reveal the
fault because it was statement
coverage. And since it
can't do both things, it's
impossible. So if you didn't
fully convey your understanding
of that, you'd get
half points for it if
you've fully described that
situation uh then you would
get full points and you can
also think about this and
explain this in a much more
simplified way rightly you
can say something like okay
assuming i i'm i'm the
daughter of two mathematicians
right so i like this idea
like let's pretend like
let's let's uh let's have
let's start by contradiction
so let's assume i can create
a test suite that achieves
100% coverage and does not
reveal the fault, right?
But then
in that test suite, there
are different subsets of
that test suite that achieve
100% statement coverage.
But my second
hypothesis is that every
possible test suite
that achieves 100
% statement coverage
reveal the fault.
So those subsets would
reveal the fault and I reach
a contradiction. And
this comes exactly by the
subsumption, right? This is
really a mathematical concept
you can think about,
subsumption as you are, you
know, a test suite is a
set of test cases and the
different coverage criteria
give you different sets.
And because certain
coverage criteria are
stronger than others, they
contain other subsets.
Maybe now was my time to
confuse them more.
I don't know.
We take turns, guys. We take
turns. This is teamwork.
Okay, but this is
the solution. We
set it, and so that
was not possible.
Okay, so let's move into—now
we start from the code
and we need to build the
task suite so we have a
class we have a method that
has been given so it's i
leave you the code here for
a second but of course you
all have worked with it
and seen it and what we are
asked we have been asked to
is to apply two different
criteria so the statement
coverage and modify
condition and decision
coverage and we want to create
we want to create a test
suite that achieves 100%
statement coverage with at
most three test cases and then
we want to create a test suite
that achieves 100% modify
condition and decision
coverage and contain at most
eight test cases. Now, there
are a lot of, there are
bonus points here because
we'll talk about this when we
look into that, but you
can, you get extra points if
you actually get, you find
what is the minimum possible
number of test cases that
you need to achieve 100%
modified condition and decision
coverage. Okay, so this
was the overall problem.
And I know that we like the
code a little better than me,
but let's reason about the
code for a second and move
to the control flow graph.
In this case, we start and
we have like we initialize
result to zero. Then we
have our first condition
that is a simple condition.
So it's just if A is different
from B, we do something.
otherwise we do something
else and we do something
is all of these that we
are asking ourselves if a
certain much more complicated
condition is if this certain
much more complicated
condition that contain three
simple elements if this
is true then result is equal
to one otherwise result
is equal to zero then And
if I go back here, so if A
was not different from B,
I'm down here, and then
result is equal to 3. And
at the end, I return result.
So if we look at this
visually, we get this
control-throw graph, and
I'll skip the entry at
the beginning so we
can fit everything that
is really important for
us to reason a second.
This is what we see, right?
and so if you look at these
we have in the graph we
have the condition here can
be true or false if the
condition is true this condition
can be true or false
and so to cover all the
statement and every branch
has a listed statement so I
need to go to cover all the
statement I need to make
through I mean to go in in
all the different branches of
these of each decision so
i need to cover for true i
go here i need to cover
for true i go here and here
i'm covered i'm covering
this statement i'm covered
result equal to one then if
a is different from b and
this condition is false i
cover result equal to two and
then if a is equal to b i
cover result equal to three
so to cover all the statement
I need three test cases
right one is to go in this
direction and is any test
cases in which a is equal
to b so and all the other
values c b c d and e I don't
really care because they
don't affect where I go
after a is equal to b so a
equal to 3 and b equal to 3
would be perfectly fine to
cover this statement that
I can cover just when a is
equal to b and when a is
different from b I'm going in
in this case and now this
is a little tricky because
it's a more complex condition
and that's precedent
overall so it means that for
this condition to be true c
is equal to zero
and d is greater
than zero or a e
is less than zero.
So if we go in this
direction, let's get any two
different values for a and
b, so a equal to one and
b equal to two. And then
for this condition to be
true, for instance, I get
a negative value for e,
and that makes the
whole condition true.
And so I'm moving down
in this direction.
Now to make the
condition false,
this has to be false,
and this has to be
false. So I get a
positive number for e,
a negative number for
d, and c different
from zero. So for
example, c equal to 1,
D equal to minus 1,
and E equal to 2. And
this would give me
this coverage, right?
So this would allow
me to cover this.
And so I need three
test cases because in
every branch, every
time I make a decision,
I also have a statement
underneath it.
And this is to achieve
100% statement coverage.
Will you want to add
something before we move?
So now to do the modified
condition and decision
criteria, we need to build
our truth table because
here the idea is a little
bit more sophisticated.
And what we are trying to
do is how any condition
within a more complex
condition within a decision
in the control flow graph
affect the condition.
So what we are trying to
do is here nothing has
changed because it's a
simple condition. is done
by, I mean, it can be
just true or false, and it
affects the decision. When
A is different from B,
I go in a direction,
otherwise I go in the other.
But this, in this decision
point, I have a much
more complicated thing,
right? And so all the
different parts of
these, all the different
conditions, c equal to 0 d
greater than 0 and e less
than 0 affect the decision
of where I'm going
in different ways.
And so with this criteria,
I'm trying to cover
where every single one of
these conditions affect
the decision that I
make. And to try to see
how this happens, what
I need to do is to build
the truth table and
try to see how all the
different conditions
affect the decision, right?
And so now we have one,
two, three, four conditions,
so four different
conditions, and so that means
I have to build a truth table
with 16 lines, right?
This is all the possible
combinations of true or
false, and so each of these
conditions can be true or
false, and the combinations are
16. Now, because when a
different from b is false,
really the value of c equal
to 0, D greater than 0, E
less than 0 are not relevant,
I can collapse all the
cases in which A is greater
than B. But when A is
equal to B, but when A is
different from B, I need to
combine these with all these
values. So I'm building
the truth table. I mean, I'm
not building it is already
built in the document i
show but let's reason about
this together right so
this is this last line here
are all the cases in which
a different from b is
false and as i was telling
you before because in that
side right over here when a
is different from b is false
the value of the other
condition doesn't matter i
can collapse that because
when a is different from b
is different uh is different
from b it's really the
value of this higher condition
doesn't really matter
but uh if now i was um
to see how i'm covering
the the graph i need to
see instead in case a
is different from b how
this different value
affect the decision in
the control flow graph
right and so i build a
true table here uh so i
try to do all the
combination of the values so
these are three elements so
there are eight combinations
um and we build it
right so now it's tricky
because there is no parentheses
so i'm i'm looking at c
equal to zero and d greater
than zero or e less than
zero so i i approach
always true table in a lazy
mode so because this is the
norm right when a is less
than zero so when a less
than zero is true this
formula is always true and
so i start like you know um
okay this is true and the
form and the condition will
be true this is true this
is true and this is true
and i don't even look at
the others right it doesn't
matter and now when this
is fault for the the truth
value depend on c equal
to zero and d greater than
zero but it's an end so they
have to be both true for
the formula to be true so
in row two c is equal to
zero uh true d greater than
zero true and so it doesn't
really matter if a is
not less than zero the
decision i will make will
go to go on the true on the
true side of the control
flow graph here i have one of
the two is false here i
have one of the two is false
They are both false. So
in all these other cases,
the value is false. And this
is how I build my truth table.
Yes?
Will, any clarification?
Did I go too fast?
No?
I cannot hear you.
It might be just me.
No, I had accidentally hit
the mute button on my mic.
um jace is better with
this stuff than i am so uh
you've done a good job of
explaining it so we'll go
with that okay let's and
then anyway you you can ask
any question you want about
this now using um using
the office hour post okay
so now the the trick is
that i want to cover all
the lines um in the minimum
number of eyes because we
want the bonus point right
to uh in which each of
these is the only one that
change and affect as and
because it's it is the only
one that change also change
the value the decision
that i will make in the
control flow graph right so now
that means i need to pick
if i look at the first
branch that i have in my
control flow graph, it means
I need to pick one test
case between one and eight,
right?
And one test case between
nine and 16, because I want
to be able to go on this side
and on this side. Because
A, different from B, is
just a simple condition, so
its root value fully affects
the path that I will take
in the control flow graph.
Now, it becomes more
complicated when i look at
the other right like one c
different equal to zero is
the condition that affect the
decision i will make on the
control flow graph okay so
i need to start looking and
say okay let's look at two
rows where the only thing
that change is c the different
from equal to zero. And so
if I look at row one and
row five, the only two things
that change is the truth
value of C equal to zero.
But this change doesn't
affect the truth value of
the overall condition. So
independently from the truth
value of C equal to zero, I
will always go in the truth
branch. So that means that
condition doesn't affect
the decision i'm making so
now i'm looking at two with
six and here again c equal
to zero is the only one that
changed but in this case
if you look if c is equal
to zero there i will go to
the uh then branch in the
in this in these when i'm
making this decision while
instead in row six that where
the only thing that changes
the value of C, I go into
the other branch. So the
pair 2, 6 is a pair in which
I value the value of C, of
the condition C equal to
zero. And so I'll put it there
as a pair that is a potential
pair to be covered. Now,
if I keep going and I
look at 3 with 7, in which
again is just C that changed,
or at 4 and 8, in this case,
the value of C does not
affect the final decision
that I'm making in my flow.
I need to do the same for
all the other conditions,
and so if I look at the
condition d greater than 0,
and I need to look at the
rows where d is the only
thing that changes, so I
look at row 1 with row 3,
d is the only thing that
changes but the final value
doesn't change, I look
at row 2 with row 4, d is
the only thing that change
and the final value change
so that would be a row that
i add then i look at the
value of five with seven
and nothing change in the
final decision and then
six and eight and nothing
change in the in the in the
final decision so at the
end the only the only
pairs that I need, that is
relevant for the modified
condition decision criteria
is 2, 4. Now, I look at E
less than 0, and then the
pairs that I need to consider
together are 1, 2, 3,
4, and 5, 6, and 7, 8,
because these are the two
pairs in which the only thing
that change is the value
of a less than zero. And
if I look at one and two,
the truth value of e less
than zero is the only thing
that changed, but that
doesn't affect the decision.
But if I look to all the
other pairs, in those pairs,
the change in the value
and the truth value of e
less than zero change also
the final value in how I
navigate the control flow
graph, so in the execution
of my program. And so the
pairs 3, 4, 5, 6, and 7, 8
are pairs that are eligible
to cover that condition.
Okay, so now I want to
cover the minimum number to
get the bonus points,
right? So for sure, I need
to choose a test case in
the group 9, 16, right?
and then i need to choose
one this case in the group
one eight but really it's
not that important which one
so let's see what are my
other constraints now for to
cover c greater than c equal
to zero i need to cover both
two and six to cover d
greater than zero i need to
cover both two and four so
two four and six that are
needed because they're my
only option to cover these two
conditions also take care of
a test case in one to eight
but also if i look here
they also cover already this
right and so if i'm adding
three then i cover this
pair and i take care also
of a e less than zero and so
if i look at two three four
six and anything in here for
for example, nine, with
five test case in my test
suite, I reach 100% coverage
in the modified condition
decision criteria. Notice
that you could have taken two,
four, I mean, you are
stuck at taking two, four,
six, right? Because these
two pairs are needed
to cover these two
conditions. But then because
you already had six, you
could have taken five
instead of taking three
and then instead of
taking nine you could
have taken 16 it doesn't
really matter so there
are still staying in the
realm of the minimum
number of test cases you
could have taken um
other test cases than the
one that we are representing
in this solution
but the minimum
number was five yeah
yep okay so now last exercise
this is this is probably
like kind of i i always
when i look at the assignment
i always think this
is kind of you know the
let's get relaxed now we are
at the end because it's
uh it's somehow a little
less mental right you really
just need to execute the
code manually might execute
the code that you have in
front of you and so you
have the code for a method
and they're asking you to
fill out the table here and
saying what is the expected
output with this value of a
and b and then to complete
certain sentences, right?
So let's just look at
the code here, and then
we look at the sentences,
right? So we need to
look, depending on the
truth value of a and b,
try to understand what
is the output, right?
So let's just, talking
aloud, execute this
code. So x is equal
to 1, y is equal to 1.
so now we do the
first rule A is
true, B is true when A is true
what happens is that X becomes
and then when B is true then
X that is now 0 become minus 1
and so when I arrive here I
divide Y that is 1 by minus 1
that is negative, so
the final value is true.
Yes? Yes. I'm doing it without
looking to the solution,
so and I'm also pretty tired,
so I'm counting on you.
Now the second row is when
A is true and B is false.
And so when A is true, we
already saw this a become
x become equal to zero
because i'm going here but b
now is uh but b now is
false so i'm going here so
i'm not changing again the
value of x so x remain equal
to zero so when i arrive
here i have a division a
division by zero and so i
have an error yep now other
combination is when a is
false and b is true so in
this case i'm here and i'm
changing the value of y
and y was equal to 1 and
it becomes equal to 2.
then i'm here and i'm
changing the value of x
x was equal to 1 and
become equal to 0
so when i arrive here
again i'm dividing
2 by 0 and so again
I have an error.
Now the last case is when
A is equal to false and
B is equal to false and
in this case in both cases
I'm just X is not touch
and so X is equal to 1
and so I already know there
is not gonna be an error
but let's see if it's
true or false what we get.
So x remain equal to 1, y
become equal to 2, and then 3.
So it's 3 divided by
1 is 3. Is it less
than 0? No. So the
result is false.
This is what I'm returning.
So then if we
look at the table,
it would be true, error, error,
false.
Now, let's keep trying
to be brave and solving
things on the flight
let's see these sentences
so the last the last
point to the end of
this exercise was to
complete these sentences
right and so they say
the following sentences
we need to complete these
sentences with never
sometimes or always so
the first sentence say
test suite with 100
statement coverage reveal the
fault in this method and
we need to say if it's
never sometimes or always
um let me turn on the brain
um and so um to reach
statement coverage it means
that i need um uh i need to
cover this statement this
statement this statement
and this statement, but
I can cover all the statement
in different ways, right?
If we look at the true
table that we just built,
okay?
I, for instance, could
cover all the statement with
this one and this one,
right? When A is true and
B is true, and when A is
false and B is false, I
cover all the statement and
I don't ever reveal. You
don't find the error.
Yeah, I don't. But, of
course, I could instead
choose this one and this one,
right? And I'm covering
all the statements
with two test cases
and find error, right?
So, never is wrong,
always is wrong.
We are now stuck with
sometimes. Sometimes.
And yes, oh, okay,
now I kind of cheated.
Okay, I was in the
wrong direction.
Sometimes was right. Now,
the second branch coverage,
but kind of the examples
I gave you now were also
examples that shows that I
actually gave a sneak peek
that the answer is sometimes.
But the two examples that
I gave you for statement
coverage right now reaches
100% branch coverage.
So because we are
covering all the branches.
Now, to cover all the
statements, you need to
cover all the branches
because there are no empty
branches here. So the
answer is still sometimes,
right? Because you can
choose a test suite that
are these two central rows
and reveal the test case,
or you can choose these two
and then reveal the error.
Yep.
last question now i'm not
gonna cheat again test suite
with 100 path coverage
reveal default in this
method so now if you think
about this there are certain
uh if you if you if you
cover all the paths you will
cover the path in which
you tweak um you change the
value of x and in in the
first part and you don't
change it back in the second
part so when you cover
all the possible combinations
of way in which you
navigate these branches you
always find the error because
all the all the possible
paths will will be you
know when you cover all the
path you need to be able to
cover all the all the tables
here because there are
all the combination in
which you cover the branch.
So when
test suite with
100% path coverage
always reveals the
fault in this method.
And that's, that
was the solution.
So there is one question in the
discussion and it
says, can we know the
points associated
with each question?
Oh, I
will. Can we know the point
associated with each question?
I think that's your
call, isn't it?
do we usually do it
for other assignment?
I don't think so.
I'm going to announce that.
Basically, I mean, you
know, you can assume they're
all pretty much similar.
If it's exactly
the same or not,
maybe it might be weighted
a little bit towards
some and not towards
others, but it's going
to be close to similar
for each of the tasks.
That's kind of what
we generally say.
Thank you, Will.
This is the moment
I miss Sheen first.
It's like, where are you?
Yeah, and I don't know
if we have anything else,
but there's another thing.
Just general feedback
about this one, since
the graphs were used
for the A6 explanation,
I found Unreal Blueprints
to be very helpful
for visualizing
problems one and three.
So I'm not sure what
Unreal Blueprints are, but
apparently somebody
found them very helpful.
Probably a site, I'm guessing.
But anyway, so if there are
any questions outstanding
at this point, now is
the time to ask them.
Otherwise, we will
be finishing up soon.
Yeah, because this
is always an office
hour that goes
long because I talk
most of the time
about the solution.
Just a reminder,
if you look, I'm in your
ear, so you watch the
solution now, but I don't
know how useful it is to
say in the office hour,
because if somebody is
watching the office hour,
they watch the solution, but
watching this solution
is a necessary condition
to be able to, what is
the English word for this
tonight? Not that very good.
I use all my mathematical
words, but if you want
to ask for a change of
grade or you disagree
on something about your
grade, you have to have
watched this solution first.
And if you arrive at the
end now you know you can
or or you understood what
you what what you made
wrong or not and uh um but
yeah so that's um completely
useless because if
somebody listened me saying
it it means they already
watched the solution so
i know when i was saying
it i say like why are you
telling this maybe at the
beginning of the office
hour would have been a
better idea but yep um Um,
but you know, if, if any
of your fellow classmates
are like, Hey, why won't
they answer my question? Uh,
generally speaking, uh,
if, if you haven't, if the,
if the student has not
attested that they've watched
the solution first, uh,
Justin will kick it back
and say, you know, you haven't
followed the instructions.
You have to have to
watch these first. And
there's a couple other things
you need to do to properly
sit. And we're not, we
mostly just do that because
otherwise we get a
lot of questions that
we really don't need
to go through this
for everyone individually
right we've already done it
yeah so if you if you if
your question is you just
don't understand what's wrong
this is the way to solve
that if you still think
yours is right after having
watched it we're happy to to
look at your grade challenge
but we're not going to
take it if it's just hey i
don't know why i got this
wrong because you can get
that from from here yeah and
somehow i think it's like
you know it's not just for
not doing it many times we
do this live in the office
hour because talking about
this might help you to
better understand and just
reading the solution because
another option could be just
publish the solution and
so it gives an opportunity
to ask additional questions
because so for us to add
additional comment and you
know like will and i for
instance we are a classic
example of people that have a
different approach right you
know what what what comes
easy and what not so you
know like i look at the
graph i look at the code
uh he explained thing in a
certain way i'll do it in
another but they are both true
and both correct right so
it helps doing it live in a
way that uh you know you
say oh yeah this is why it's
different they they told
me in two different way now
i understand i should have
looked at this other thing
right it's uh doing it
live it's um give give more
more explanation than just
publishing the solution yep
any more question there
do not seem to be any more
and so 50 minutes 40
a second we did very
well yeah oh we are
so we are set the clap
so i'm I'm feeling
very proud tonight.
Hopefully you're all getting
started on the second
phase of the individual
project at this point.
And we'll see you
next week. Next
week. Yeah, next
week. For week 14.
For week 14.
Hopefully Shin will
be here to tell
us that because I
will have forgotten.
Me too, probably. Have
a great week, everyone.
Bye.